var questions = [{
	"question": "Which of the following solution turns milky white upon adding ethanol and water?",
	"option1": "A slice of potato",
	"option2": "Bread",
	"option3": "Palm oil",
	"option4": "A piece of apple",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "In complex multicellular organisms, eukaryotic cells become _________ for specific functions.",
	"option1": "Turgid",
	"option2": "Specialised",
	"option3": "Smaller",
	"option4": "Bigger",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "How many oxygen molecules at a time could be carried by a haemoglobin molecule?",
	"option1": "3",
	"option2": "4",
	"option3": "2",
	"option4": "1",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Which is not a function of golgi bodies?",
	"option1": "Determining which proteins are to be transported outside the cell",
	"option2": "Packaging macromolecules for delivery to other organelles",
	"option3": "Sorting and processing proteins",
	"option4": "Intracellular digestion",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Which of the following is a double membrane bound organelle?",
	"option1": "Lysosomes",
	"option2": "Peroxisomes",
	"option3": "Ribosomes",
	"option4": "Chloroplast",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "The most common protein found in animals?",
	"option1": "Haemoglobin",
	"option2": "Albumin",
	"option3": "Keratin",
	"option4": "Collagen",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Many prokaryotic cells do not have __________________.",
	"option1": "A capsule surrounding the cell",
	"option2": "One or more flagella",
	"option3": "Microtubules",
	"option4": "One or more plasmids",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Which indicates an indirect evidence for evolution?",
	"option1": "Addition of extra features in cells",
	"option2": "Presence of basic features in cells",
	"option3": "Existance of all life on Earth as cells",
	"option4": "The fact that all cells arise from other cells",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "The enzyme responsible for forming hydrogen bonds during the process of DNA replication?",
	"option1": "DNA ligase",
	"option2": "DNA polymerase",
	"option3": "DNA helicase",
	"option4": "Lactase",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "What happens when a Biuret reagent is added to a solution of free amino acids?",
	"option1": "The solution turns mauve/purple",
	"option2": "The solution turns milky white",
	"option3": "The solution turns brick red",
	"option4": "The solution remains blue",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "If a specimen appeared 20mm in length under a microscope with a magnification of 1,000 times, what is the calculation of the actual length?",
	"option1": "0.2",
	"option2": "2",
	"option3": "0.02",
	"option4": "0.002",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "Select the incorrect sentence out of the following:",
	"option1": "Magnification and resolution are not dependant on each other",
	"option2": "Resolution is the ability of optical instruments to produce images that are clearer, finer, and sharper",
	"option3": "A high magnification does not always guarantee a high resolution",
	"option4": "Magnification is the ability of optical instruments to make an object bigger",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "The lungs are in the _________ surrounded by the ___________ which enclose an airtight space.",
	"option1": "Pleural membranes, thoracic cavity",
	"option2": "Trachea, bronchus",
	"option3": "Thoracic cavity, pleural membranes",
	"option4": "Bronchus, pleural membranes",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "A similarity between transmission electron microscope and scanning electron microscope?",
	"option1": "Both can attain the same amount of magnification",
	"option2": "Both can be used to view the insides of each organelle",
	"option3": "Both produce a 3D visual image",
	"option4": "Both are used to observe dead organisms",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "Stomata does not close in which of the following circumstance?",
	"option1": "Low temperature",
	"option2": "High light intensity",
	"option3": "Darkness",
	"option4": "Low humidity",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "An essential feature of alveoli which contributes towards efficient gas exchange?",
	"option1": "The alveoli are surrounded by capillaries",
	"option2": "They have thick walls",
	"option3": "The alveoli are present in the lungs",
	"option4": "Alveoli are less in number",
	"answer": "1"
}]	